"矮子告急"
Low man scrapped, yo.
"他快揭不开锅了"
He all the way down.
"但我们明天有新来头..."
But we going to start fresh on the latest tomorrow...
"打北边过来"
Down from up North.
没啥问题啊
No problem.
没啥问题?
No problem?
是的 他们在说一个叫"Lohman"的家伙
Yeah, yo's talking about some guy named Lohman,
感染了"链球菌"...像是病了
Who's down with strep... Iike he's sick.
最后一部分呢
And the last part?
最后一部分是说
And the last part is something about
他现在如何开始追一个时髦女之类的
How he's gonna start up a Fashion Lady or some shit.
时髦女?
Fashion Lady?
我很了解Perkins Homes 和Latrobe Tower的方言
I'm fluent in the Perkins Homes and Latrobe Tower dialects,
但还不怎么会Franklin Terrace的话
But I haven't quite mastered the Franklin Terrace.
他说他们在平房区的货卖完了...
He's saying they're sold out in the low-rises...
所以明天他们要开始卖新品
So tomorrow they're gonna start fresh with a new package.
- 这是你听到的? - 再听一次
- That's what you hear? - Listen again.
"矮子告急"
Low man scrapped, yo.
"矮子"代表平房区
Low man, meaning the low-rise pit.
"他快揭不开锅了"
He all the way down.
那里的存货所剩无几
Is down to scraps on the last package.
"但我们明天有新来头..."
But we going start fresh on the latest tomorrow...
"打北边过来"
Down from up North.
明天 他会开始卖新品
Tomorrow, he'll start fresh on the latest package.
天 你们怎么都听懂的?
Damn, how you all hear it so good?
“黄金海岸号贩奴船驶往棉花田”
"Gold Coast slave ship bound for cotton fields...
"奴隶就在新奥尔良的一个市场被贩卖"
"sold in a market down in New Orleans."
- 这它妈的是什么 - 滚石乐队
- What the fuck is that? - Rolling Stones.
"Brown Sugar"的前两句歌词
First two lines to Brown Sugar.
我敢说这首歌你听过不下五百次
I bet you've heard that song 500 times,
但你从不知道歌词 对吗
But you never knew, right?
我曾把耳朵贴在立体音响上
I used to put my head to the stereo speaker
一遍又一遍地重复播放
And play that record over and over.
难怪你现在这样
That explains a lot, actually.
"那就等黑仔咯?"
So, wait on black, yo?
什么是"黑白配"?
What's white on black?
是"等黑仔" 对吧?
Wait on black, right?
我都能听出来
Even I heard that shit.
黑仔是Stinkum的代号
Black's code for Stinkum.
我们从他的传呼里得知的
We picked that up once we got on his pager.
所以 会往平房区送4袋 每袋价值1千元的补货
Now, there's gonna be a re-up of four G-packs in the low-rise court.
Stinkum会去送货
Stinkum is on the re-up
而且会在中午前后进行
And it's gonna go down around noon.
这些你都确定?
Are you sure about all that?
倒过来看
Turn it upside down.
四条连续竖线 每条代表一袋...
Four hash marks in a row, one for each G-pack...
"LO"代表平房区
"LO" for low-rises.
"12"代表时间
12 for the time.
"S" 是指Stinkum
"S" for Stinkum.
你们花了多久搞懂的?
How long to figure that out?
四五个小时吧
Four or five hours.
你们花五小时就坐在那看呼机信息?
You sit here looking at beeper messages for five hours at a time?
不知道 能看出点东西还是挺有趣的
I don't know, it's kinda fun figuring shit out.
火线重案组 第一季 第七集 一次逮捕
The Wire S01E07 One Arrest
* When you walk through the garden *
* You gotta watch your back *
* Well I beg your pardon *
* Walk the straight and narrow track *
* If you walk with Jesus *
* He's gonna save your soul *
* You gotta keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
* All the angels sing *
* About Jesus' mighty sword *
* And they'll shield you with their wings *
* And keep you close to the lord *
* Don't pay heed to temptation *
* For his hands are so cold *
* You gotta help me keep the devil *
* Way down in the hole *
做人得有操守  -- Bunk
你在拖我后腿 Sanny
You're not helping me out here, Sanny.
- 警长 我... - 我只是请你帮一个忙....
- Major, l-- - I ask you for one fucking thing....
- 我知道 但我不能... - 这几个月来 我都罩着你
- I know, but I don't-- - All these months, I'm carrying you.
我坐在这 看着案件一件件堆起来 对吧?
I'm sitting here, watching case after case stack up, right?
这些都是你的案子 它们都还没破 Sanny
These are all yours, and they're all open, Sanny.
去年 你的破案率是40%
Last year, your clearance rate was 40%.
今年 破案率更低了
This year, it's less than that.
我接了一些棘手的
I caught some tough ones.
Dunker:警方俚语 出自"灌篮"一词
现在好破的不多了
There's not a lot of dunkers in there.
Mike 你是挺会办容易的案子 我会给你的
Mike, you're good on the dunkers. I'll give you that.
说起容易破的 你的破案率大概
Shit, comes to dunkers, you solve probably
十件破了六七件吧
6, 7 out of 10.
但是不好破的呢?
But a stone fucking whodunit?
这么算不公平 少校
That's not a fair assessment, Major.
公平? 它妈的什么是公平?
Fair? What the fuck is fair?
我有个警探在外 无法无天
I got a detective out there, unsupervised,
搞他自己的特侦组
Running his own special ops unit...
有机会就摆我一刀
Burning me every chance he gets.
我的工作不是去整另一个警察
It's not my job to fuck another cop.
不是你的工作?
Not your job?
这么说吧 警探
Tell you what, Detective.
我他妈的会非常公平的 现在我给你个选择
I'm gonna be so fucking fair I'm gonna give you the choice.
要么给我点McNulty的小报告
Either bring me something on McNulty,
要么去做你的工作
Or go out there and do your job.
- 挑一件 随便哪件 - 警长...
- Pick a file, any file. - Major--
选一件谋杀案 破了它...
Pick a murder and solve it...
或者把McNulty带给我 没第三个选择
Or bring me McNulty, there's no third choice.
Stinkum会带个跑腿的
Stinkum will have a runner with him.
跑腿的负责带货
The runner's gonna be holding the package.
你发现他们后 打开警笛
When you get them, ride the bumper.
- 让他知道我们在场? - 是的
- So he knows we're there? - Right.
需要的话还可以亮出警灯
Lay on the blue light if you need it.
这样 跑腿的就会逃走
Now, the runner's gonna bolt.
- 我去抓他 你伺机抓Stinkum - 不
- I got the runner, you stay with Stinkum. - No.
- 我抓跑腿的 他抓Stink? - 不是
- I got the runner, he takes Stink? - No.
你们都去抓跑腿的
You both take the runner.
- 让Stink逃走? - 没人逃走
- And Stink gets away? - Nobody gets away.
如果我们拦下Stink的车... 我们就要交出证据
If we pull in Stink on a car stop now, we got to give up PC...
意味着我们要停止监听
Which means we got to give up the wire.
我们设计这一切 不只是为了抓批卖个两天的货 对吧?
We didn't set all this up for two days' worth of coke, did we?
我们抓住跑腿的 放长线钓大鱼
We snatch the runner, stick a hook in him and go back fishing.
而监听录音和从车上跑出来的马仔
And between the wiretap and the runner bolting from the truck...
能让我们随时去抓Stinkum
We got a charge on Stinkum any time we want it.
我们还追查了一些旧的谋杀案
We're also edging back into old murders,
发现了一些新证人
Pulling up fresh witnesses.
还有一些可以没收的在外资产
And there are assets to be seized down the road,
用来洗毒资的资产
Stuff that fronts for the drug money.
- 比如什么? - 一家脱衣舞俱乐部...
- Like what? - A strip club...
西区的几间洗衣店 一家三A级的拖车公司...
A couple of Westside laundromats, a triple-A rated towing company...
一家殡仪馆
A funeral parlor.
殡仪馆?
A funeral parlor?
他去年在Gwynn Falls买了一家
He bought out one in Gwynn Falls last year.
他的钱无处不在
The money's going everywhere.
这些还只是我们从Avon的一个女人 向别人吹嘘时知道的
That's just what we know from one of Avon's girls bragging to a friend.
天知道他还有多少我们不知道的
I mean, God knows what else he's got that we don't know of.
Barksdale名下什么也没有
Understand Barksdale's name is on nothing.
他总是幕后操控
He's always a step or two removed.
这是能建功立业的案子 法官
It's a career case, Your Honor.
看着我 Jimmy
Look here, Jimmy.
你拼错了"culpable"(有罪)...
You misspelled "culpable"...
你把"then"和"than"弄混了
And you're confusing "then" and "than."
T-H-E-N是个副词
T-H-E-N is an adverb
用来分隔 衡量时间
Used to divide and measure time.
McNulty警探捅了篓子
"Detective McNulty makes a mess...
"然后"他要摆平
"and then he has to clean it up."
谢谢你把每个词解释一下
Thanks,teach,I mean, it's great that you're going through every word--
别和T-H-A-N弄混了
Not to be confused with T-H-A-N,
这个通常是用在比较级之后
which is most commonly used after a comparative adjective
比如说
Or adverb, as in:
Rhonda"比"Jimmy聪明
"Rhonda is smarter than Jimmy."
明白了?
Yeah?
要求继续进行监听的理由 已经陈述得够多了
Look, there is more than enough indication of progress to justify continued intercepts.
我会再签发30天的监听和复制的指示
I'll sign an order for 30 more days on all taps and clones.
一份给法院 一份给州检察官?
One copy to the court, one to the State's Attorney?
- 还有什么需要的吗 - 什么 问你要吗
- Anything else you need? - What, from you?
我想这没我的事了
I think I'll go see a man about a dog.
这一直是我的荣幸
It's always a pleasure,
Pearlman女士
Ms. Pearlman.
你的职业涵养和综合能力...
Your professional demeanor and your overall competence...
在市政府平庸无能的背景下
Stands in stark contrast against the usual municipal backdrop
闪闪发亮
Of mediocrity and indifference.
讽刺吗 法官
Sarcasm, Judge?
不 你只要再干十年这个工作
No. Another 10 years of this nonsense,
我可以预见到你 穿着Baltimore地方法院的法官袍
And I see you wearing the robes of the District Court for Baltimore City.
或者是疯人院的约束衣
That or a straitjacket.
天哪
Jesus.
我真想把我的鸡巴插进她那里
I would love to throw a fuck into her.
红头发 小雀斑....
The red hair, freckles....
你不觉得吗 Jimmy?
Don't you think, Jimmy?
在法庭上重要的是...
As in all matters before the Court,
要和法官想的一样
I think whatever the Judge thinks.
过来 Jimmy
Come on, Jimmy.
坐下
Sit.
谈谈
Talk.
- 12-14 - 怎么样
- 12-14. - What's up?
Preston东侧
Eastbound on Preston.
车里坐着Stinkum和护驾的一个年轻人
Stinkum and a young boy riding shotgun.
他们停在了红灯前
They're at the light right now.
拍到了
Got them.
看看他玩的把戏
Let's see how he plays it.
妈的
Fucking shit.
他随时可能跳车
He's gonna bail any moment.
便衣来抓人了!
Jump out!
向Druid Hill方向逃窜 700号街区 嫌犯穿着灰色上衣
Bail-out on Druid Hill, 700 Block, suspect wearing gray sweats,
向着院子那跑去
Running into the court.
我操
Fuck me.
- 收摊 - 警察
- Close shop. - Police.
妈的
Shit.
矮子 快点 快点
C'mon, shorty. Step. step.
他抓不到你的
He ain't man enough for you.
那是补货 快点
- Re-up! go. - re-up. yo.
你好 警官
Hello, Officer.
快跑 快点 小子
Run, man! Move, motherfucker.
白人追上了
White man walking!
快点 矮子 那是我的补货
Yo, move, shorty, that's my re-up, yo!
操
Goddamn.
他回来了
He's coming back!
- 投降吧 小子 - 截住他 截住他
- Give it up, son! - Cut him off, cut him off!
抓住他
Yo, get him!
我去拿包
I got the bag!
他往右了
He's going right.
拿到包了
Get the bag.
快点啊 哥们
Yo, move, man!
怎么样 怎么样
What's up?
- 妈的 - 臭小子
- Damn. - motherfucker.
妈的
Damn, motherfucker.
打赌你们不会对白人这样
Bet you don't do that shit to a white man.
你们它妈的只会放过他
Y'all get the fuck away from him.
他什么也没做
That man ain't did nothing to nobody.
四袋 成品
Four packs. Street-ready.
- 12-08 - 12-08
- 12-08. - 12-08.
Lex的800号街区需要一辆囚车
Need a wagon inside the 800 block of Lex...
- 在院子内 - 收到 12-08
- inside the court. - 10-4, 12-08.
亦可理解为白粉 所以大家都笑了
你们谁有烟吗?
Anyone got a smoke?
你和你的头儿处的怎么样
How are you sitting with your bosses?
Rawls上周想结了这个案子
Rawls tried to close this thing down last week.
想起诉一些没胜算的谋杀案 暴露监听行动
Blow the wiretap by charging some weak-sister murders.
谁制止了他
What stopped him?
Daniels
Daniels.
- Daniels? - 我也不敢相信
- Daniels? - I couldn't believe it either.
我准备投降放弃时 Daniels跳了出来
I'm ready to throw in the fucking towel, Daniels stepped up.
是吗
Yeah?
你怎么不来找我
Why didn't you come to me?
你不信任我了吗 Jimmy
You don't trust me no more, Jimmy?
出自"用10美分打个投币电话告密"
谁向报社记者出卖了我 法官大人?
Who dropped a dime to that newspaper reporter, Your Honor?
你从哪来的?
Where you been?
现在得花35美分才能打通电话
35 cents these days, before anybody'll cough up a dial tone.
不 是50分
No, it's 50.
一周后我就要回凶案组上夜班
I got another week before my homicide shift flips to night work.
不回去的话 Rawls就会找我麻烦
I'm not back with them, Rawls sticks it to me.
你在这有朋友
Well, You got a friend here.
要是情况继续恶化
Worse comes to worse,
Pearlman还可以去找她的上司
Pearlman goes to her bosses.
州检察院还是喜欢你的 Jimmy
The State's Attorney's office still has some love for you, Jimmy.
比起那些不喜欢我的
All due respect,i'm starting to worry more about the people
我更担心那些声称喜欢我的人
Who claim to love me than the ones who don't.
现在吗
Now?
好的
Yeah.
有人呼叫了Stringer Bell
Somebody's hitting Stringer Bell's pager
在高层围院的2号公用电话
From the Number 2 payphone in the Tower Court.
- 现在吗 - 现在
- Now? - Now.
怎么样
What's up?
- Freamon - 看到Stinkum了
- Freamon. - Visual on Stinkum.
我们被条子弄丢了四袋
Yo, we lost four to 5-0.
- 什么 - 我们丢了四袋
- What? - We lost four.
你它妈的干嘛告诉我这个
Yo, why the fuck are you telling me this?
我迟点再和你说
I'll talk to you later.
他以为这是我拉屎啊?
Does he think I can just pull it out of my ass?
不完成作业就不能出去 是吗?
Can't go outside and play till your homework's done?
不为Rawls破了这案子 我什么都做不了
Can't do shit till I clear this case for Rawls.
多久的案子了?
How old is it?
又旧又没戏
Old and cold.
从你身上开刀?
Yours to begin with?
朋友 你霉星高罩
Then, my friend, you are double-fucked.
狗娘养的
Motherfucker.
婊子养的
Son of a bitch!
把名片给我
Give me the card.
你个变态 无情的杂种
You sick, heartless bastard.
把名片给我
Come on, give me the card.
* 她是个吉普赛女郎 *
* She was a gypsy woman *
Laurie夫人?
Madame Laurie?
你瞧不起?
You scoff?
它妈的的LaRue夫人 Jay?
Madame fucking LaRue, Jay?
比你强的人在他们没有头绪的时候
Better men than you have turned to this lady...
都会去找这个人
In their dark night of dead ends.
你不是吧
You're not serious.
我从不拿LaRue夫人开玩笑
I don't joke when it comes to Madame LaRue.
那个女人 她有过人的天分...
The woman, she has an unexplainable gift...
在调查谋杀案上
In matters of death investigation.
她超越了理性
She transcends the rational.
给她打个电话
Give her a call.
他被撂倒在这里
He's dropped here,
这一侧被垃圾箱挡住了 但是...
So the dumpsters cover it from this side. But...
这边每个有窗户的都能看见
everyone over there with a window had a view.
这是奖励给我们俩童子军的荣誉勋章啊
Merit badge for two good little Scouts.
女士
Ma'am,
需要我们帮忙吗
You need some help with that?
我可以的
I'm all right.
这是我们的荣幸
Please, it's our pleasure.
让我猜猜
Let me understand.
你们在这里晃荡
Y'all hang around the projects,
一黑一白...
White and black together...
西装革履
Ties and jackets on,
想要帮助推购物车的女士或者别的什么人
Looking to help ladies with their shopping carts and whatever else.
警察 对吗
Police, right?
恐怕是的 女士
Afraid so, Ma'am.
是关于不久前的谋杀案吧?
About the murder a while back, right?
那个修理工?
Maintenance man?
被告请就座
The defendants can take a seat.
法官马上就到
The judge will be in shortly.
我能拿这份档案吗
Can I take the file?
- 给你 - 谢谢
- Here. - Thank you.
不好意思 女士
Excuse me, Ma'am?
嘿
Hey.
警探?
Detective?
- 我需要带走一个 - 是吗 哪个
- I need to pull one out. - Yeah, which one?
我看看
Let's see.
吸毒 可卡因 吸毒 偷窃 吸毒...
Dope, coke, dope, theft, dope...
流浪罪 可卡因 盗窃未遂 吸毒...
Ioitering, coke, attempted theft, dope...
吸毒 盗窃 吸毒 现在的指控是...
Dope, theft, dope, and the charge du jour is...
非法藏有 可卡因
Possession, to wit, cocaine.
但你需要他?
But you need him?
我需要他
I need him.
行 他到毒品法庭去...
Okay, he bounces over to drug court...
承认藏毒 同意缓刑...
Pleads to possession and agrees to probation...
答应接受治疗
With ongoing treatment.
- 这样就行? - 这样就行
- That's it? - That's it.
好的
Okay.
我是和你朋友Bubs一起的 你想出去 对吗
I'm with your boy Bubs. You want out, right?
是的
Yeah.
承认非法藏毒 说服法官...
Plead guilty to possession and convince the drug court judge...
你会改过自新
You want to get your shit clean.
毒品法庭?
Drug court?
答应治疗...
Shake it off in treatment...
去参加聚会 他们让你尿时就尿
Go to some meetings and pee when they tell you to pee.
不进监狱?
No jail?
- 不进监狱 - 我现在就能出去?
- No jail. - I'm out right now?
等你走完流程
Soon as you're processed.
好的
Okay.
死者从这条路走来
Dead man was coming this way
另一个人跟着他
And another man was walking behind him.
肯定有对他说了什么
Must've said something to him,
因为他中枪前回头了
Because he turned around before he got shot.
- 你认识开枪的人吗 - 不 警官
- Do you know the man who did it? - No, sir.
他长什么样
What'd he look like?
- 谁 - 坏人
- Who? - The bad guy.
浅肤色 中等身材
Light skin, medium height.
身上没什么肉
Didn't have no meat on him.
年纪大小?
Young or old?
不算年轻
He wasn't young.
好的 如果你把我的搭档当作受害人...
Okay, if you pretend my partner here is the victim...
我是拿枪的那个....
And I'm the guy with the gun....
这么近吗
This close?
不
No.
这样吗
Like that?
是的 差不多
Yeah, that's about right.
- 如果你再次看见这个人... - 我不能....
- Do you think, if you saw this guy again-- - I didn't....
女士 请别害怕
Ma'am, please, don't be afraid.
从我坐的地方看去 他背对着我
From where I was sitting, his back was to me.
没事 你做得很好
It's all right, you done good.
如果有任何麻烦 打电话给我们
You have any trouble at all, you call us.
她不能指认凶手
She can't make a positive ID.
我的人Omar可以
My man Omar can.
一个有着无数前科的强盗?
A stickup artist with a half-dozen priors.
就是你的目击证人?
That's your eyeball witness?
她证实了他说的细节
She corroborates him on the details,
近距离枪击
Right down to the close-range shot.
Omar还说如果我们找到Bird 就能找到那把枪
We've also got Omar saying if we jack Bird, we'll get the gun.
说他太笨不会丢掉的
Says he's too stupid to throw it off.
那么 她和Omar之间
So, between her and Omar,
一把匹配的枪能帮我们窜起案情
A match on the gun gets us over.
正如你说的...
It happened like you said...
像一个计划
Iike it was a plan.
就是一个计划
It was a plan.
你的地址是?
What's your address?
Fayette街734号
734 Fayette.
你住几室?
What's the apartment?
小子 你住几室?
Kid, what apartment?
小子 你的房间号?
Come on, kid, what's the apartment?
11-M
11-M.
好的 11-M 不是很容易吗?
Okay, 11-M. Is that so hard?
你的出生日期?
What's your DOB?
注意点 小子
Come on, kid.
什么
What?
是他
It's him.
谁
Who?
Kevin Johnson?
你饿吗?
You hungry?
火腿起司? 金枪鱼?
Ham and cheese? Tuna?
我要Reese牌的
I want a Reese's, yo.
花生黄油杯
Peanut butter cup.
喝的呢?
Drink?
罐装茶
Tea in a can.
行
You got it.
去底下的售货机
Go down to the machines.
一份花生黄油杯 和一罐立顿茶
Get a peanut butter cup and a can of Lipton's tea.
那个混蛋都不敢看我
Motherfucker can't even look at me.
- 我们重新开始怎么样 - 重新开始?
- What say we start over on this? - Start over?
我的律师说 那桩事能让我把你们通通告倒
My lawyer said I got a case against y'all for this shit.
去他的律师
Fuck the lawyers.
我在说的是人生 Kevin
I'm trying to talk about life here, Kevin.
游戏已经让你付出了代价 不是吗?
Game already cost you, right?
我知道 已经超过了本应有的
More than it should have, I know.
这是谁的错
Whose fault is that?
他的 我们的
His. Ours.
或许是我的
Mine, maybe.
我觉得我亏欠了你
Thing is, I feel like I owe you something here.
所以我问你有何打算
So, I'm asking how you want to carry this.
想要脱身吗?
You want to get out?
想在余生有些作为吗
You want to do something else with the rest of your years?
那就来找我
You come see me.
茶卖完了
Tea was sold out.
可能是明天 可能再过一阵
Might be tomorrow, might not be for a while.
但你觉得准备好做出改变时 打电话给我
But when you're ready for something different, give me a call.
我会记住
I'll remember.
那混蛋觉得他能用根糖果条就能收买我
Motherfucker thinking he can pimp me over a candy bar.
我觉得可能和毒品有关
I'm thinking it might be a drug thing,
或是单纯的劫案
Or maybe straight-up robbery.
你是爱尔兰人吗?
You're lrish, no?
意大利人 Santangelo
Italian. Santangelo?
Santangelo
Santangelo.
Saint Angelo
Saint Angelo.
古代殉道者 意大利Licata的守护神
Early martyr, patron saint of Licata, ltaly.
身上插着刀还在为刺客祈祷
Prayed for his killer with the knife still in him.
但这不是Saint Angelo的召唤
But it's not Saint Angelo calling.
是Saint Anthony想帮你
It's Saint Anthony who wants to help you.
他想?
He does?
非常想
Very much.
他难道不是你丢了东西时 该祷告的人吗?
Ain't he the guy you call when you lose something?
你确定这是Anthony?
You sure that's Anthony?
去死者的坟墓 把这个雕像埋进去...
Go to the victim's grave, bury the statue...
等一小时 够足一小时 不能偷懒
Wait an hour, a full hour, no shortcuts.
然后挖出它 直接回家
Then dig it up. Go straight home.
当你睡觉时 把它握在耳边
When you go to bed, hold it to your ear.
然后他会告诉我是谁干的?
And he tells me who did it?
我想现在轮到我挑了
I think it was my turn to pick.
嗯 绝对该我了
Yeah, definitely my turn.
之前你在B&O就让我失望了
You had me down at the B&O the other night.
在你把我拉到Sugar Hill Tavern之后 记得吗
After you dragged me to the Sugar Hill Tavern, remember?
不
No.
嘿 Turk
Hey, Turk.
这样美妙的夜晚Nadine去哪了
Where's Nadine this fine evening?
Gainesville 靠近福罗里达州 要在她姐妹家住整整一周
Gainesville. Been down in Florida at her sister's all damn week.
说来难堪 不过
Shame to say, though.
没有女人滋润的男人会转性啊
Lack of pussy will change even a good man's demeanor.
真是美妙
Sweet as can be.
Marla
Marla.
很高兴见到你 记得我丈夫吗 Cedric
Good to see you. You remember my husband, Cedric?
记得 见到你很高兴
Yes, I do. Nice to see you.
Marla和我都在GBC的城市开发委员会
Marla's with me on the GBC's downtown redevelopment committee.
就是她在会上戳醒我
She's the one that prods me awake at the meetings.
那是个无聊的会
That was drastic stuff.
- 每个人都昏昏欲睡 - 最后一个特别长
- Everybody was nodding off. - That last one was so long--
- 失陪一下 - 好
- Excuse me. - Sure.
我想这是几年来最好的一张候选人名单
I think it's the best ticket in years.
警局中尉来五百元一份餐的筹款会?
$500-a-plate fundraisers for a police lieutenant?
即便在这个城市 也能构成一条严厉异常的惩罚
Even in this city, that constitutes cruel and unusual punishment.
选单上的哪位成员如此吸引了你?
And which member of the ticket has so energized you?
市长? 议会主席?
The Mayor? Council President?
还是遗嘱登记人?
The Registrar of Wills, maybe?
如果是市长 看见他的话或许能认出来
The Mayor, I might recognize if I saw him.
其他的 我肯定需要看看身份照
For the rest, I'd pretty much need B of I photos.
你说得没错 中尉
You're not wrong, Lieutenant.
在这个州 竞选海报 和疑犯照片的差别很微小
In this state, it's a thin line between campaign posters and photo arrays.
突击测验
Pop quiz.
市议员?可能是西区的?
City council? Eastside, maybe?
州议员
State senator.
Clay Davis 来自第39区
Clay Davis, from the 39th District.
预算委员会副主席
Vice-chair on the budget committee.
这样的反映速度 你永远当不上警长
You'll never make Major at this rate.
失陪 我要去尽我的本职
Excuse me, while I do my duty
去拍些议员的马屁了
And kiss some senatorial haunches.
Clay 很高兴再次见到你
Clay, nice to see you again.
来 我们去吧
Come on, let's roll.
你不签字吗
Ain't you gonna sign it?
不 等聚会结束了 你回来拿
No, you get that back when the meeting's over.
你不留下来 我们就不签
And if you don't stay, we don't sign.
就是这么个流程
That's how it works.
来吧 我想看看这里
Come on, I want to see the show.
Bubbs
Bubbs.
10:我们坚持自我反省
10: We continue to take personal inventory...
如果做错了 勇于承认
And when we are wrong, promptly admit it.
11: 我们通过祈祷和冥想
11 : We sought through prayer and meditation
增进心中与上帝的交流
To improve our conscious contact with God,
理解他...
As we understood Him....
有些面孔我好久没见到了
I ain't seen some of these faces in so long,
以为他们死了
Thought they were dead.
不是一回事吗
Same thing, ain't it?
完成这些之后 灵魂会觉醒...
Having had a spiritual awakening as the result of these steps...
我们试着把这些信息给其他上瘾者...
We try to carry this message to other addicts...
在我们的人生中实践这些信条
And practice these principles in all our affairs.
今天的讲话者是 Waylon...
Today's speaker is going to be Waylon...
如果你来过这些聚会 一定知道他
Who, if you come to these meetings, you have to know.
你们都知道我是Waylon 一个毒瘾者
Hell, you all know I'm Waylon, and I'm an addict.
你好 Waylon
Hi, Waylon.
事实是 我想要戒毒的心愿
And the fact is that I want to be clean today
强过我想要爽一把的念头
More than I want to be high.
我知道这是对的
I know that's right.
来这儿很好
It's good to be here.
来到任何干净的地方都很好
Hell, it's good to be anywhere clean.
即便是在Baltimore
Even Baltimore.
目前我已经戒了好几天了
I been clean a few 24 hours now,
但我还是很肯定我的疾病想要我死
And I'm still dead certain that my disease wants me dead.
我在这和你们说
Yeah, I'm in here with you all, talking shit about
我有多么坚强 我意志多么坚定
How strong I am, how strong I feel...
但我的疾病就在外面的停车场上
But my disease is out there in that parking lot,
挑拨着我 跃跃欲试
Doing push-ups on steroids waiting for the chance
想要再次整垮我
To kick my ass up and down the street again.
我手上的 脚上的伤疤
Scars on my hands, on my feet...
两次心内膜炎
Two bouts of endocarditis...
丙肝把我的肝脏搞得
Hep C and whatnot knocking down walls
千仓百孔 溃不成军
And kicking out windows in my liver.
我失去了一个好妻子
I lost a good wife...
坏女友
Bad girlfriend,
和任何一个愿意借钱或是帮我的人的尊重
And the respect of anyone that ever tried to loan me money or do me a favor.
当掉了我的小卡车 自行车
Pawned my pickup, my bike...
我的National Steel牌吉他
My National Steel guitar...
还有祖父留给我的集邮册
And a stamp collection that my granddad left me.
当我几乎一无所有时...
And when it was almost over for me...
我站在角落里 连个尿罐都没有
And I was out there on them corners not a pot to piss in,
所有认识过我爱过我的人...
And anyone that ever knew me or loved me...
都咒骂我 你知道我告诉自己什么吗
Cussing my name, you know what I told myself?
我说 "Waylon 你做得很好"
I said, "Waylon, you're doing good."
我这么说了
I surely did.
我觉得我是上帝选中的瘾君子
I thought I was God's own drug addict.
如果不是上帝要我去爽
And if God hadn't meant for me to get high...
他不会让吸毒的快感这么完美
He wouldn't have made being high so much, like, perfect.
我知道我心中还想再来一次...
Now, I know I got one more high left in me...
但我严重怀疑 自己能不能再康复一次
But I doubt very seriously if I have one more recovery.
如果在座各位
So if there's anybody out there
有跌入过这种谷底...
That sees that bottom coming up at them...
我说的你会懂
I'm here to talk sense.
我不在乎你是谁
I don't care who you are...
做过什么
What you done...
对谁做过
Or who you done it to.
你在这
If you're here...
我也是
So am l.
说得好
That's right.
芥菜籽小组(名字寓意"有远大前程的")会派发钥匙链
The Mustard Seed Group gives out key chains...
给戒毒了一段时间的人
For stretches of clean time.
如果你觉得你能得到 请来领取
So if you've earned it, come on up and get it.
有人坚持9个月了吗
Does anybody have nine months?
有人坚持6个月了吗
Does anybody have six months?
有人坚持3个月了吗
Does anybody have three months?
有
Yeah.
有人坚持一个月了吗
Does anybody have one month?
现在 给这间屋子最重要的人
And now, for the most important person in this room...
有没有人坚持了24小时?
Does anybody have 24 hours...
或是真诚地想要活下去?
Or a sincere desire to live?
有的 很好
Yeah, all right.
我们今天上午才吸过
We shoved off this morning.
上帝赐予我力量
"God grant me the strength...
让我接受不能改变的
"to accept the things I cannot change...
有勇气改变我能做到的
"and the courage to change the things I can...
还有区别两者的智慧
"and the wisdom to know the difference."
比分多少
What's the score?
Orioles领先 4比3
Orioles, 4 to 3.
Bernie Williams 刚上了二垒
Bernie Williams just doubled, though.
他们总是让Yankees队追上来 一直是
They always let the Yankees back into it, always.
不 他们今年有个厉害的后补
No, they got a bullpen this year.
- 谁在投球 - Buddy Groom
- Who's pitching? - Buddy Groom.
你为谁开车
Who you driving for?
Marla Daniels(他老婆)
Marla Daniels.
我真想抢劫这房子
I'd love to crack this here crib.
是吗
Yeah?
很有赚头 很有赚头
Good day's work. Good day's work.
那报警系统呢
What about the alarm system?
我可以把这没屁用的线给绞断了
Shit, I'd wire that weak-ass thing back on itself...
踩足马力 穿过法国门梁
Pull the truck up, bust through those French doors.
- 行啊 - 当然可以
- That'd work. - Yes, indeed.
一路上可以卖了多数好货 但有一些
Sell most of this good shit around the way but some of it,
比如艺术品 必须运到纽约去
Like the art and all, I might have to run it up New York.
我叫Damien Price
Name's Damien Price.
但大伙都叫我Day-Day
But I mostly go by Day-Day.
我是Cedric Daniels
I'm Cedric Daniels.
但大伙都叫我中尉
But I mostly go by Lieutenant.
看 换上Roberts了
Look, they're bringing in Roberts.
你在这啊
There you are.
我要你见一个人
There's somebody I need you to meet.
- 继续 - 耶
- Go on. - Yeah.
- 全脱了吧 - 把它们挤在一起
- Take it all off. - Rub them together like that.
明白吗 混蛋
See here, motherfucker.
你得把Gant的事算在Bird身上
You got to put this Gant thing on Bird...
你得在另一件案子上下点工夫了
And you got to do something with that other case...
那个年轻女孩
The young girl.
Diedre Kresson
Diedre Kresson.
你得以谋杀罪同时起诉这两件案子
You need to be able to charge both them murders...
然后你就站在Rawls的上风了
And then you walk that on up to Rawls.
现在 你看 Jimmy
Now, you see, Jimmy...
对于你这种混球来说 现在是难关
Here's the hard part, for an asshole like yourself:
你得破了这些案子
You just got to give him
当礼物送给他
Them clearances like a goddamn gift.
然后你还要继续拍他马屁
And then you still might have to kiss his ass...
大概还要三四个月
For about three, four motherfucking months.
你必须这么做
You're gonna have to do it.
三四个月?
Three or four months?
必须的 Jimmy
Got to, Jimmy.
其他的都它妈的为时已晚
Too fucking late to do anything else.
你会变成白人马屁精
You gonna be one ass-kissing white man.
你知道我为什么这么尊敬你吗 Bunk
You know why I respect you so much, Bunk?
并不是因为你是好警察
It's not 'cause you're good police.
因为...那是狗屁 对吧?
'Cause, you know, fuck that, right?
是啊 去它的狗屁
Fuck that, yeah.
不是因为我到凶案组时
It's not 'cause when I came to Homicide,
你教我的那些很酷的事...比如...
You taught me all kinds cool shit about....
我也不知道 无所谓了
I don't know, whatever.
无所谓
Whatever.
是因为轮到你来操我时
It's 'cause when it came time for you to fuck me...
你非常温柔
You were very gentle.
真它妈的说对了
Damn right.
因为你本可以...
See, 'cause you could've
把我从车库里拖出来
Hauled me out of the garage...
把我压在警车前盖上
And just bent me over the hood of a radio car.
但你没有 你很温柔
But no, you were very gentle.
我知道那是你的第一次
I knew it was your first time.
我想要做得特别一点
I wanted to make that shit special.
是的 兄弟
It was, man.
的确是的
It fucking was.
- 收起你它妈的钱 - 不 这算我的
- Take your fucking money back. - No, this is mine.
拿回去 你个老婊子
Take it back, you old whore.
Turk
Turk.
我能再来一轮吗
Can I get one more?
你好 哥们
What's up?
- 他们在上面 是吗 - 是的 他们在上面
- They up there, right? - Yeah, they up there.
嘿 Dee
Hey, Dee.
你有机会了 让我教教你
You get a chance, man, let me pull your coat to something.
有些我们能做的事
I got a little move we might could do.
等回来找我 好吗
So get with me after, okay?
行 没问题
All right. Most def.
我打给Bell的唯一原因是那些黑鬼...
The only reason why I even called Bell was because these niggers--
你不该在电话里说这些 你知道的
You're not supposed to talk shit on the phone and you know that.
你好 老兄
What's up, bro?
谁告的密
Who's snitching?
没人
Nobody.
你确定吗
Is you sure on that, man?
你那先是抢劫 然后被警察突检
You done had the stick-up, then the jump-out.
- 现在 他们盯上了Stink - 我的人都守口如瓶
- Now, they running up on Stink. - My crew, we tight.
好吗
All right?
没人有多余的钱 我都检查了
Ain't nobody holding no extra money. I checked all that.
也许是你的人闯红灯 或者尾灯没打之类的
Maybe your ass just ran a stop or had a taillight out or some shit like--
你觉得我会带着四万元闯红灯?
You think I'd run a stop with $40,000?
当然不
Fuck no.
哥们 我不知道
Nigger, I don't know.
事情是不对劲
Something is up.
所以今天回去
So go down there today...
告诉为你工作的那些马仔
Tell them hoppers you got working for you down there...
规矩马上要变了
That this shit is about to change.
Stringer会过去 亲自安排这件事
Stringer gonna come down there, he gonna run through the changes.
直到一切正常前 平房区暂时歇业
Until this shit is straight, the Pit is dead.
事情是 为什么他们不抓Stink
Thing is, why they didn't pop Stink?
警察抓了那男孩 没收了货
Knockos took the boy and the package,
他们可以通过车牌抓到Stink
And they got Stink by the tags on the truck.
你去警局报告车子丢了 是吧?
You took that down to the police and filed a report, right?
那车啊... 我扔在Cold Spring巷了 伙计
Truck, I ditched that shit up off Cold Spring Lane, man.
你还没听到缉毒警有什么动静吧?
You ain't heard nothing from the knockos yet, right?
没
No.
它妈的这算什么?
What the fuck?
他们逮住了从那车里下来的四袋毒品
They catch four packs popping out the truck.
却连车牌都没看到?
They don't even get the plate?
它妈的在搞什么啊?
What's all this shit?
出事了 伙计
Something's up, man.
肯定出事了
Something is definitely up.
我要去个地方 必须去
I got somewhere I gotta be.
帮我在Daniels那挡一下 好吗
Cover me with Daniels, will you?
混蛋
Asshole.
Herc...Carver
Herc, Carver.
- 怎么了 - 怎么了
- What? - What?
过来
Come here.
他们两个是怪胎
Them two is freaks.
不知道哪冒出的两个混蛋抢了毒品
Stash-finding motherfuckers popped the package from nowhere.
你在说谁
Who you talking?
瘦瘦的黑鬼和一个很丑的警察
Skinny black motherfucker and that ass-ugly knocko.
戴帽子的白人
The white boy with the ball cap.
放倒Bodie的那个?
The ones who jumped Bodie?
蝙蝠侠和罗宾汉
Batman and Robin.
不错嘛
All right?
- 嘣 - 你们被他们记住了 小子
- Bang. - You got them, baby.
- 我是蝙蝠侠 - 不觉得
- I'm Batman. - I don't think so.
- 蝙蝠侠是白人 - 难道罗宾汉是黑人?
- Batman's white. - And Robin's black?
你也听到了 你是很丑的白人
You heard the hopper, you're the ass-ugly white guy.
"神奇小子"(罗宾)为什么不来吸吸我的蝙蝠鸡鸡
Boy Wonder, why don't you suck my bat-dick?
它妈的给我滚
Get the fuck outta here.
为什么你不给我个签字 "一日先生"?
Why don't you sign this for me there, Mr. One-day Man?
希望他们要你尿检时  上帝能对你仁慈点
God have mercy when they piss you, boy.
你是说我理解的那个上帝?
You mean the god of my understanding?
不 我们得给你弄些干净的尿
No, we gotta get you some clean piss, you know...
好让你带去缓行执行办公室
So you can take up into your probation office.
嘿 Bubs
Yo, Bubs.
我们认识的人里 谁能有干净的尿啊?
Who the fuck do we know with clean piss?
你们准备起诉这一件了?
So you're ready to charge this one?
只要有运气找到枪就行
If we luck into the gun, yeah.
然后我们一起去抓Bird
And then we tag-team Bird.
如果人赃俱获 就交给联邦调查局
If we get him with the gun, we take it federal.
至少判五年 而且他还有重罪的前科  那会更久
Five years minimum, and he's got prior felonies... it's a lot more.
有抓捕的地址吗
We got an address we want to hit?
我们正在和线人合作
We're working with informants.
一旦有线索 就出动
As soon as we get something, we jump.
"午后有股暖气团"
...warm air for the afternoon...
"部分地区晴 有风 可能有雷阵雨"
Partly sunny, windy and warm with a chance of thunderstorms...
"最高气温83华氏度 而到周五时"
High up to 83, and then on Friday,
"风和日丽 最高气温接近70华氏度"
Clearing and windy with a high near 70.
"这是来自WTOP电台的最新整点天气预报"
Weather updated around the clock on WTOP radio.
"我是气象频道的气象学家Dave Lew"
I'm meteorologist Dave Lew at the Weather Channel.
"这里是WTOP广播电台"
This is the WTOP radio network.
你有担心自己被看到吗?
You worried about being seen?
如果有谁对我和你们混在一起 看不顺眼
If anybody got a problem with me spending time with y'all...
我会义不容辞地把枪塞进他嘴里
I'd be much obliged to stick my gun straight in their mouth.
怎么样
How's that work?
Bird今天没有出现
Bird not up in the mix today.
如果除了诨名 我们能掌握他别的名字
If we had more than a street name,
也许就能查到他的地址
Maybe we could come up with an address.
我能说什么 在这里 Bird就是Bird
What can I say? Out here, Bird just Bird.
那你们就打算在这守株待兔了?
So, what up, you all fixing snatch him from out here?
计划是这样
That's the plan.
他不会带着家伙出来 大家都不会
He don't pack down here, none of them do.
这是规矩
And that's the rule.
如果你想找到枪 你得去找楼里的小子
Now, if you want iron, you gotta go to one of those kids up in the towers.
- 我们要那把枪 - 这就难办了
- We need the gun. - Then y'all got a problem.
既然不知道他住哪 那当然难办
Without knowing his crib, we definitely got a problem.
除非你们知道Bird在哪嗑药
Not unless y'all know where Bird like to cop.
- 什么 Bird也吸毒? - 在楼里 他不会
- What, Bird gets high? - Not in the towers, he don't.
Avon不让他的人吸 这是另一条规矩
Avon ain't having his people using. That's another rule.
"永远不吸自己的货"
"Never get high on your own supply."
如果我要找Bird先生
Now, if I was hunting Mr. Bird...
我会考虑有最好的货的Red Dilly
I would consider the best package to be the red Dilly...
在Carrollton那
That's over there in Carrollton.
当然 如果我是你们这种"父母官"的话
That's if I have to be constabulating like you all.
Carrollton?
我还知道 当你们去抓他时 最好...
I know one thing, when you all run up on him, you all best be more...
更小心点
Careful, that is.
为什么
Why is that?
Bird肯定会毫不犹豫地开枪
Bird will throw down without thinking, for sure.
Poot
Poot.
Wallace在哪 老兄
Where Wallace been at, man?
不知道
I don't know.
连个影子都见不着
He in the wind.
Wallace不行了
Wallace been fucked up.
自从他们抓到那个抢劫的男孩
Since they got that stickup boy, you know?
把他那样放在车上示众
Put him on the car like that.
Wallace就不出声了
Wallace all quiet and shit.
有时候连门也不出
Don't even come out his room some days.
我在找Dee 看见他了吗
I'm looking for Dee. You seen him?
Dee
Dee.
闲着呢?
Chilling?
什么事
What's up?
你来公房这儿干嘛?
What're you doing down in the projects?
我有事 老兄
I got something, man.
好事
Something right.
过来
Come on over.
铺子呢?
Where the shop at?
今天没货
Nothing today.
瞧是这样的 如果你要更多的货
See, that's the thing, 'cause if you need more of that...
我有路子
I got this connect.
是吗
Yeah?
我在俱乐部里认识的 华盛顿来的
This guy I know from the club, he from D.C.
他在新奥尔良进的货  从那里的牙买加人手里
He got this thing through New Orleans, these Jamaicans down there.
新奥尔良?
New Orleans?
他们货多 Dee
They're offering weight, Dee.
- 我舅舅知道吗 - 不 瞧...
- My uncle know about it? - No, see.
这货我做东...
This thing on the side for me...
数量上 纽约也才及它的四分之一
I got enough to turn a New York quarter on it...
但我没有像你一样的分销渠道
But I don't have what you got right here with the distribution.
你明白我说的吗
You see what I'm saying?
我说 Dee
I'm saying, Dee,
和他们之间的风险我担着
I'd be taking all the risk with them peoples.
一旦我拿到了货就送到你这儿 你帮忙卖出去
Once I have the package, I bring it down here to you, and you put it out.
挣的钱我们平分
We do an even split on what comes back.
行吗
Right?
让我想想 好吗
Let me think on that, all right?
我们终于有盼头了 明白我说的吗?
Finally get some ends for us. You see what I'm saying?
明白
Yeah.
是的 当然
Yeah, most def.
- 我走了 - 好的
- I'm out. - yeah.
- 走好 - 行 好好想想
- Be good. - all right. Think on that.
五元帽子 在这里 五元一个
$5 hats, right here. $5, baby, $5.
五元 大家 这里五元一个
$5, yeah. Everybody, $5 hats right here.
我们要盯哪个门?
Which door are we watching again?
商店隔壁的那间空房
The vacant next to the store.
就是那个射击房
That's the shooting gallery.
他还在里面?
Is he still in there?
Greggs守在后面 我们在前面 不如你来告诉我
Greggs is on the back and we're on the front, so you tell me.
好
Yeah.
五元帽子 在这里 五元一个
$5 hats, right here. $5, baby, $5.
就在这里
I got you right here.
好好遮遮你那脑袋 明白我的意思吗
Cover up that head of yours. You know what I mean?
心动了吧 五元一个
Can't beat that, right? $5.
五元帽子 这里 五元帽子
$5 hats, right here. $5 hats.
- 五元帽子 先生 - 操你丫的
- $5 hat there, mister. - Fuck you, man.
抓住他们
Take them.
嘿 小妞!
Shorty.
把手放在后面
Where's it at? Get your hands back.
Get your hands back.
- 抓到了 - 我抓到他了
- got him. - I got him.
放开我
Get off me, man.
它妈的放开我
Get the fuck off me.
- 抓住脚了 - 死条子!
- I got the feet. - Bitch-ass cops!
抓到了
There we go.
操你妈的!
Fuck, man.
看看我们搜到了什么
Yeah, look what we have here.
- 宝贝 - 它妈的放开我
- Baby. - Get the fuck off me.
我的手
My hand.
- 死贱人! - 它妈的闭嘴
- Fucking bitch. - Shut the fuck up!
太紧了
Shit is tight, man.
我们该把沙发放在那 对吗
We should leave the couch right there, right?
是的 把它放在那
Yeah, leave that shit right there.
很好看 不赖
That's nice, that's straight.
怎样
So?
什么事 String?
What's the deal, String?
你们多久换一次藏货的地方?
How often you all changing the stash?
自从被抢之后 每晚都换
Every night since we got jacked.
你们人里有吸毒的吗?
Anybody on the team getting high?
没 伙计 只有那些望风的老油条会吸
No, man. Just the old touts.
不过他们接触不到钱 也碰不到货
And they ain't handling no money, no vials.
你们都检查过那些空房子吗?
You all been going in and out of the vacants?
确保缉毒警员没在那设陷阱?
Making sure them narcos don't set up in there?
当然 肯定的
Yeah, for sure.
没人打手机 也没有室内电话吗
I got no cell phones, no house phones neither, right?
没有 只有这些呼机
No, man, nothing but these pagers
还有那边的公用电话 就这些
And them pay boxes over there, that's it.
行 把那些狗娘养的拆了
All right, tear them motherfuckers out.
什么
What?
把那些电话拆了
Tear out them phones.
现在起 你们想用公用电话 就到外面的街区去
From now on, you all need a payphone, you walk a few blocks..
一天内同一台电话只能用一次
And you do not use the same phone more than once a day.
听到了吗
You hear me?
- 听到了吗 - 听到了
- You hear me, right? - Done.
好的 Bey 把那些玩意拆了
All right. Bey, tear them motherfuckers out.
来吧 伙计
Come on, man.
哥们靠边 把电话挂了
Man, come on. Get off the phone.
服务受阻
我们本想挂...
So, we wanted to hang...
天鹅绒背景
The velvet backdrop...
上面有凌志车和斗牛犬
With the Lexus and the pit bulls...
但它还在干洗店
But it's still out at the dry cleaners.
但说真的 伙计
But seriously, folks,
我们真的想给陪审团展示
We really wanted to show all the jurors...
当你离开这小审讯室时
That you left our little interrogation here
你身上的伤口
Without any more scuff marks...
没有比来时的多
Than what you brought in.
操你娘的 死胖子
Fuck you, fat man.
"操你娘的 死胖子"
"Fuck you, fat man."
我以为我们是朋友来着
I thought we were friends.
那把枪正在楼下做弹道测试
That gun is downstairs now, in the ballistics lab.
要是追查到一个死去的州证人身上
It comes back on a dead state's witness,
你就等着去死吧
Then you're gonna see death row.
明白了吗
You up for that?
吸我的鸟吧 死拉子
Suck my dick, dyke cunt.
我的律师在哪
Where's my lawyer at?
怪胎 吃B的
Freak. Cunt-eater.
你只有一个机会 你个蠢货
You got one chance, you stupid motherfucker.
说出是谁指使你去杀William Gant
You roll back on the people you killed William Gant for...
要不然你就等着玩完吧
Or you gonna eat the whole meal.
告诉你吧
Tell you what...
放开我 走过来
Gimme this hand back and step to me,
我会把你的三个洞都干了
And I'll fuck you in all three holes.
这个小子真它妈臭屁
Fucking charmer, this one.
贱人
Bitch.
你们有狗屁!
You ain't got shit on me.
你们该进去一个
One of you should go in.
她有麻烦了?
Is she in trouble?
Kima 他这么下去 她会剁了他
Kima? He keeps this up, she'll cut his ass.
你们连狗屁都不是
You ain't shit!
你们有个狗屁!
You ain't got shit on me!
你就是我的目击证人咯?
So, you're my eyeball witness?
为什么这次站出来?
So, why'd you step up on this?
Bird很逊
Bird trifling, basically.
他居然杀了个老百姓
He killed an everyday working man and all.
别误会 我也做坏事
Don't get it twisted, I do some dirt, too...
但我绝不会枪击一个无辜的人
But I ain't never put my gun on nobody who wasn't in the game.
做人得有操守
A man must have a code.
毫无疑问
No doubt.
老兄 我在别处见过你
Man, I know you from somewhere.
是吗
Yeah?
来凶案组之前 我在西南区
I was in Southwestern before I came to Homicide.
在Frederick路工作
Worked Frederick Road.
不 我说更早之前
No, I mean, back in the day.
你念的是Edmondson 对吧?
You go to Edmondson, right?
是的 比我大几届
Yeah, you was ahead of me.
我记得你是我见过第一个
I remember you was the first brother
玩那个耍棍子运动的黑人兄弟
I ever seen play that sport with a stick.
那叫什么来着
What's it called?
- 曲棍球 老兄 - 是的
- Lacrosse, man. Yeah. - For sure.
我是主攻手
I was All-Metro attack.
预科班的小子看到Bunk冲过来时
Prep school boys used to pee themselves
会吓得屁股尿流
When they see old Bunk coming at them.
既然这样 老校友
So look here, homey.
既然你记忆力这么好
Seeing as how you're being all charitable with your recollections...
关于未破的案子你还有什么内幕?
What else you got in the way of open murders?
- 关于Barksdale的? - 随便什么
- Going to Barksdale? - Going anywhere.
你要我追忆多久以前的?
How far back do you want me to go?
多远都行
As far as you need.
谋杀案是不变的
Murder stay murder.
谢谢
Thanks.
枪吻合了
Gun matches.
你完了 Bird
You're done, Bird.
你还有最后的机会为自己找条活路
Last chance to grab a little something for yourself on a deal.
吃我的屎先 你个城里的白贱货
Eat my shit first, you downtown white whore.
这就对了
Yeah, that's right.
把这个丑死的拉子也带上吧
Take this ugly-ass cunt-eater with you, too.
我带着手铐呢 老兄
Yo, I'm cuffed, man.
你至少给我个公平的机会吧
You gonna at least give me a fair chance, right?
别这样 别这样对我
Come on, man. Don't do me like that, man.
注意:请勿单独留下囚犯
你个肥猪!
You fat fuck!
把手铐拿掉
Take these handcuffs off, man!
你说的是Fulton和Baker吗
Fulton and Baker, you say?
发生在去年 复活节之后的几天
It happened last year, couple days after Easter.
一个叫Neecee的女孩
This girl by the name of Neecee.
她大概30 35岁这样
She about 30, 35.
Denise Redding
Denise Redding.
是的 我看到了
Yeah, I got it.
我会被诅咒的
I'll be damned.
Bird真会挑衅 对吧?
Bird sure know how to bring it out in people, don't he?
喂
Hello?
Lindsey的案件 是吧?
The Lindsey case, right?
不 Lindsey...Martin Lindsey
No, Lindsey. Martin Lindsey.
谁是它妈的Denise Redding?
Who the fuck is Denise Redding?
你们对他怎么了
What the fuck did you do to him?
给你的 Mike
Here's yours, Mike.
我它妈的都不记得这一件了 我发誓
I don't even fucking remember this one. I swear I don't.
已经破了
Well, it's down.
我们的小子给了口供
Our boy gave us a statement,
两个证人 一个能指认你的枪手
Two witnesses and an ID of your shooter.
顺便带上我们的恭维
Take it with our compliments.
Sanny
Sanny.
这个时候你在这干嘛?
What are you doing downtown this time of night?
它妈的LaRue夫人?
Madame fucking LaRue?
我得谢谢你 Jaybird 你它妈的救了我一命
I gotta thank you, Jaybird, you saved my fucking life here.
唯一搞不懂的是
Only thing I can't figure is I asked
我求助的是Lindsey案 不是这件
For help on the Lindsey case, not this one.
Mike...
去它妈的吉普赛女人
Fuck the gypsy shit.
这些才是救你的人
These are the guys that saved your ass, right here.
多谢
Thanks.
Jimmy
Jimmy.
我们得谈谈 兄弟
We gotta talk, man.
关于Rawls的
It's about Rawls.
什么计划?
What's the plan here?
酒后乱性的星期二之夜?
Drunken fuck on a Tuesday night?
- 还是已经是星期三的早晨了? - 我没喝醉
- Is it Wednesday morning? - I'm not drunk.
是Rawls
It's Rawls.
他要卸了我的警徽
He's going after my badge.
什么
What?
他们要搞我 Ronnie
They're gonna do me, Ronnie.
他们要搞我 我爱这它妈的工作 可他们居然要搞我
They're gonna do me. I love this fucking job, and they're gonna do me.
进来
Come on.